[Music]
you want to miss
this what's up y'all we in the same spot
we started with the very first video if
I'm not mistaken I think I did my first
video like this cuz I didn't know how to
Vlog I think I just propped it up like
this is but yeah the bathroom Echoes cuz
I'm in my master bedroom bathroom so
this is where all the magic happens this
is the bathroom that started the YouTube
probably was wondering what that bump
what I was circling on my face it's a
bump eliminated oops is this right here
definitely recommend it's helped my skin
no this is no promo either like this is
real deal for the Bros that's watching
that girl facial hair you know how
irritating your skin can get how
irritated it'll get after you shave and
stuff but that exfoliating brush I was
using in the beginning it helps a lot
with reducing the redness and irritation
this is the sauce that I ain't never
really told nobody at the end of every
face wash routine you go in there with
some sunscreen
afterwards telling you I don't care if
you black white purple pink
whatever you go in there with the SPF at
the end of your routine you really could
just put that on there and that only
like moisturizer and that I got to do a
lot but I'm no dermatologist I don't
know skin like they do but I'm just
saying what I know works for me so the
SPF on top is just cherry on top I've
never posted this
so but it's definitely
fire but yeah today is a solar
eclipse and I thought why not get it on
film I don't know where I'm going to get
the glasses from last time we had one
was like 2017 if I'm not mistaken that's
when I lived with my grandma and she had
everything on that you know parents
grandparents a lot of them they be they
go above and beyond for their child she
I got me my sister she got everybody in
the house the glasses and we all was
watching it sitting outside chilling we
just going to wing it hopefully we can
come across some I'm going to go check
out the store right quick and see if
they got some all right yall so I just
talked to my brother and he said know
where they at and bro we live in the
same area so he said he going to just
come scoot me we going to come we going
to go and get him uh so yeah y'all about
to
see some more of my family all right y
so we made it to where we going we about
to get these Shades hopefully we can
find him if not my ass going to be in
the house cuz I'm not about to be blind
yall we made it here they got the shades
we got to wait in the
line I don't know how much it is but we
definitely going to get some where you
trying to eat from
yeah got twin with me again y'all know
who's with me same folks different day
they got that 37 on that
motherucker have a good day got on huh
you got you got a on yeah just
one
F I'm saying you can't
seate day timeing about people eyes
going to be turn hold this for me bro
while I put this in my thing
this do not post that it's going to be
in that mug all right y'all so we got
the glasses uh my sister-in-law
returning something at the store so we
about to come in here and get that
probably get some food and then I'm
going to go go to the gym but it's
supposed to start at 300 something
so and I'm out here busted like I'm
literally ready to go to the gym like
I'm ready to go to the gym and all but
safety
first but I'll see y'all next whenever
I'm either eating or back in the car one
of the two but see yall there super
random but something's telling me to say
this I don't know who needs to hear it
y'all know I'm not I'm not no mind
reader or nothing but I just speak when
it cross my mind but something is
telling me to tell somebody that's
watching that you are outgrowing who you
are with who you're surrounded by I'm
not saying relationship as in boyfriend
girlfriend I'm saying that you're
outgrowing maybe a friend group or
something of that nature and I just
wanted to tell you that before I got
this food cuz it just came on my mind as
I was getting ready to turn on my camera
and I'm just like something just is
telling me over and over in my head to
just say that and it's nothing deep it's
just something was telling need to tell
you guys that you might be out growing
the people that you're with and it's
time to alter it's a lot of stuff that
has to change in order for you to
prosper and that's exactly what is going
across my mind right now
so very random but something just told
me that you need to sit back and
evaluate and I'm not sitting here
telling you what to do y'all know me I'm
not not telling you that I'm just saying
something came across to tell me that I
need to tell someone that's watching
that you're outgrowing the people that
you're with and you have to change your
surroundings and it's okay to be alone
it don't get no better than that cuz
once you break through that that alone
time like okay there's a bunch of stages
with the alone Thing Once you break free
from that alone stuff and um like you'll
be alone and then after alone you'll
feel lonely and then you'll just be
alone but you'll be content while you're
alone once you get to that content place
of being alone nothing else will bother
you like I love being by myself I know I
with my family but I love being by
myself I'm about to get a sub right now
and then we just going to chill until we
get this
um till we get this uh eclipse going on
Jazz getting
something Welly you up for something
serious you already went to Walmart uhuh
ho ass [__] a want to hold the
door I might get a sub
though
you already recording mode you said do
what oh
yeah yeah I be getting that shf ham but
instead of ham I just get double
turkey [__]
[Music]
fire you ain't know what to
do I got I know what I want can I get um
turkey and cheese sub LGE
white can I get double turkey on it
please appreciate it can I get it all
the way with spicy
mustardy mustard yes ma'am light mayo
pickles too
please yes
ma'am huh I'm a big
[__] your hand uh Turkey
large
just a sandwich uh and just a water cup
I get some
[Music]
water hey y'all I ain't going to lie I'm
cheap I be lying I said a water cup you
know was lemonade my cup damn my baby is
so dirty look at her uh brother
uh okay then I just got approved by
granny in there that the hair is valid
so anybody that's hating on it I don't
give up this is real raw this a real raw
day today I'm not doing too much editing
to this I'm just going to post a lot of
this just raw just to let it do and see
how it is cuz I want to try doing longer
videos and um yeah
so but what I was saying before I got in
the car I mean before we got out the car
I meant that bro I meant every single
word like with the separation and the
real reason why you guys found me is
because what I just said like separating
yourself from the old crowd or SE
separating yourself from the people that
you really love cuz like sometimes
what's best is to love people from a
distance and
um it's it's hard but it it really isn't
that hard cuz as as long as you focus on
loving yourself none of that other stuff
really matters like yeah I went outside
and stuff like that the other the other
day and stuff like that I mean I'm
trying to be there for people you know
what I'm saying that's been there for me
and stuff like that and that's that's
fam so
but that outside thing just every time
I've went outside this year I've learned
or I've seen why I'm supposed to be at
home or why I'm supposed to be working
why I'm supposed to be out the way and
when I say work is this cuz I saw
somebody ask me like to take take them
somebody commented and asked me to take
y'all with me through a day and life of
my work job this is my work this is my
fullblown work like I don't work for
nobody but me this is all I do so this
is a real raw day but I'm going see y
when when I get to the house I'm going
to show yall the sub and then by that
time the eclipse will be going on so
2024 eclipse is on the way so if
something happens after this
y'all hey this is what what the world
look like before it happened but I'll
see y'all soon it's the final
product the sub so I'm about to eat this
and I'm going get up with y'all cuz I
need to take my time with this so after
we eat I see y the I see y with the
sun this
[__] [__] eyes
burning
15 that's a
bumblebee
[Laughter]
shast
hurt make it sat there and get a
check disability dumb ass
ass
that [__]
[Laughter]
[__] the way that [__] ain't getting cut
out is
crazy oh my
God it looked like your body collapsed
when you did that [__]
one time for the
[Laughter]
Vlog ho [__] got put a pop in
that
brother that's what I'm going to put in
there
brother bro let me let me let me show
bro please let me show
them bro please let me show them bro
come on
[Laughter]
bro bro
[__] what do you be doing in your free
[Laughter]
time [__] just took a picture staring
at the sun his eyes is going different
way
come here you looking they
can't that crazy oh my God what we going
to do if [__] start falling at the
sky they making it seem like [__]
about to be dying and [__] demons about
to be walking around I remember that
what was that 2012 we was all supposed
to the world's about to end on December
something we won't see Christmas and
[__] I was sitting on the computer
watching the countdown andit [__] I
looked outside I'm like [__] what the
[__] yeah the comedian eyeballs is
[Laughter]
crazy oh
[__] just waiting for the meter Rod to
hit
me
what the
meteroid metero [__] what did you call
it a met
I text him a Lista what I
[Music]
want no
Oro
oregano
origano hell no boy I ain't never heard
nobody call oregano
oregano
look oh that's hard
what's going on you guys it's the next
day it's rainy as you can
see it's one of them darker days when I
just want to sit in the house but I'm
about to get lunch right now and um I'm
about to uh do some work as well so I'm
going to take y'all with me in here I'm
about to get some
Panera if you can see can you see that I
don't know if you can see it but I'm
about to go into oops forgot the
windshield wiping I'm about to go into
to Panera I I done already packed the
shake I done packed up everything I
needed for the day so we about to go to
Panera get some work done and eat it's
raining Raining though not bad
but get my book bag and then we'll be
good to
go we got some stuff to
do o
we let me wipe this camera off before it
fls
okay yeah it's the next day the eclipse
was nothing like I thought it was but
y'all know me I'm about to go get this
work in
but first I got to get the the main work
done then I can go get the gym work in
but we about to get a salad or
something
but I'm super super hungry
yeah no problem
[Music]
bro are you guys in
line are you
sure um how you doing good can I get a
uh chicken Caesar salad ho yes please
what else for you um just a water cup
water cup mhm and it's right here oh yes
we do you have a card I don't what's the
name that you call out Nate
Nate okay it's going to be
127 said she wanted a
cookie you anything all right have a
good you too thank you excuse me sorry
no you
good
you
this one don't have the watermelon the
watermelon uh lemonade that they got
fire y'all know me water cup for
whatever
[Music]
drink is
beautiful
[Music]
beauty is so self-destructive I'm losing
all my you don't want to meet me halfway
then I don't want it I don't think that
it's fair cuz once she was my homie you
made mistakes and I made one and then
you gave up on me yeah like a
doublesided coin I flip it the outcome
is always the same tell me I'm childish
but baby you don't even act your age if
I st down to your level then I'll be a
shame we grown now you said it yourself
while you keep playing
GES it's so peaceful in there oh it's
not running too bad anymore it's all
peaceful in from there I'm about to
start rocking with them I'm not going to
lie but okay I I just finished with all
of my
work I had to do them taxes boy I've
been waiting till the last minute I
ain't want to do it
but had to do it
so now we are on the way to you
knowwhere and I found my lunch box that
I got from like High School in the uh
attic at my house so from now on anytime
I have to like do something like on the
run or something I'm just going to put
my lunch box in my car like I did
today
I'mma put my lunch box in my car like I
did
today with my um what's it called with
my protein shake easy I'm going to
provide a a course soon to show you how
I gained all this weight and stuff like
that but we about to go to the gym it
seems like I always record on leg day
for some reason I don't know why it's
like every time I record me going to the
gym it's normally on a leg day I think
the last time though was like chest but
it seems like I always record on leg day
for some reason I don't know why
like you would expect me to want to
record on
like back and by or like chest and back
type day like you would expect me to
want to record on those type of days but
it seems like I always want to record on
leg day for some reason and that's why a
lot of my videos of me at the gym always
are at the end because I'm doing core
because I like core and I mean I do core
every day so
but I also want to like pop out with a
surprise one day like I want to catch
people off guard with how I look but I'm
just taking a day byday step by step but
that salad I just had from Panera fire
bro like I swear when you eat it in
there it tastes better than when you eat
it at um like when you take it home or
take it to go they be stingy with the
sauce they give you one small little
ranch packet but in there flooded the
bowl but now I'm on the way to the gym
so I'm about to go get my life together
out here and then and um yeah so we're
just having a nice little chill day
y'all want to see what I do in the
daytime see what I be doing so I'm
taking y'all along with me um this like
a two-day type of Vlog but we not
complaining we kicking it so I'll see
y'all at the
gym what you got camera
rolling listen you lost
weight you can come in here exercise all
day and do all types of different [__]
I'm trying to get big [__] I can't just
sit in here here playing curls and then
do legs and then do abs it's not going
to get me nowhere told you this it's not
going to get me nowhere you got to do
specific muscle groups no I'm asking one
question who told you that
nobody what you
mean bro it's a bat bro I ain't never
seen no skinny [__] g off just coming
in here throwing [__]
around I don't seen big [__] do it
though but I ain't never seen no skinny
[__] my size
just come in here and not have like no
set thing of what they going to do today
you don't know skinny like I know skinny
I used to work out like that I didn't
know what push pool meant and I used to
just go in there and copy
[__] get this [__] for that 25
boy I'm talking about bro I just walked
in and he going to make me drop
25 oh I'm saying come on man
it's
okay today is
situps so we do off off and on nah [__]
making oh he's cheating he's cheating
I'm talking about I'm already in a whole
25 he
suen imagine you just getting ready to
do your 25 you start off with your 25
have a good have a good day by the time
you get the 10 by the time you get the
10 this what he
doing and he right
back my tell you in the and I want my
money straight up one up in my
[Music]
face
[__] we creating monsters in here
[Music]
yeah what's the word real more paper
than a librarian Dirty Money never bu
facing the truth and it seem to get
scarier it's real life I can't go
nowhere PE negle and opinions going
everywhere soers cry and Sh tears key to
my heart is not here I want to know
what Dirty Money never clean it f love I
do not need it cross the line once you
beat it can't force it on you to see it
you sit in agony now you go after me
shooting me bad and you claim me the
better me what is he giving it I do not
get it you realizing this is the way
life go seeing my kids grow old and go P
my backs and hit the rooll feel like
home no more open my chest up for you
pictures in my head of her toxic don't
know what to do all is hurt I don't
deserve through more paper than a
librarian Dirty Money never bu facing
the truth in the seem to get scarier
it's real life it can't go nowhere PE
neglecting opinions going everywhere so
just cry sh tears key to my heart is not
here I want to know
what I know what they got close on my
partner so she can get closer to me
[__] you be tricking they [__] on your
brothers but claiming they want you for
Keys devious where see it this why I
keep leaning for love and drugs but I
don't know what love like know what that
draw for Life internally bleeding my
heart keep beating it's loud inside my
head tonight hoping that I See the Light
hoping that I make it right falling back
inside my hole again 3 years ago I was
sleep in the van out of oy to clear out
my head don't want to visit it ever
again I was stuck inside the dark place
heart breaks with
[Music]
heart me alone
I'm more a librarian Dirty Money never
bu facing the truth and the seem to get
scary it's real life it can't gowhere
negle the going everywhere just crying
sh my heart is not I to
know a month ago could I have done this
I would have said n about this
[__] my words put another one
on try
to huh I'm try to let him go I want to
see this
go
feel I
can yeah come
on it's been a
while want to get high
high about you and I hope that we can
make it right how you looking tight I'm
[Applause]
taking I Look to You to roll my dosage
I've been feeling lonely one calling I
know a home
L we smoking the best before we
floating looking for a man with all
motion your body I control
it I'm the man with
emotion ABX y i control it I'm the man
she call on for all of her emotions I'm
the one you fall on when you feel like
it's no one I got a big heart hope you
see it
I thought about you and I hope that we
can make it right love how you looking
them tight I'm
taking love and I Look to You Roll my i'
been feeling lonely one calling I
know I showed you my weakness but I
don't want to be your crion I said you
feeling super I'm your man and I feeling
Collide when I'm with you I for better
now my feelings all right don't want you
for your body baby I want you for your
mind don't want be the weak link but
when I'm around you
[Applause]
[Music]
baby all right y I'm
tired um I recorded a good bit of the
leg day I know y'all really don't give
up because I'm not the biggest dude with
it comes to a lot of stuff so but that's
all progression we'll look back at this
video a year from now and we'll see the
progression we'll see
how I was just doing six ples on a hat
squat to maybe we'll
say uh 10 like a year from now we'll
just see
but I didn't want to just do the Abs at
the end of it I wanted to show youall a
little bit of what I was doing in here
so but now I recorded a good I think I
recorded about four workouts out of the
eight so now we about to get in the
coure um me and the Jim Bros might do
some uh some circuits together if not
I'll do them by myself but we're about
to get into that right
now Su guys post gym just ate some
spaghetti slam
that today was a good day
um we got a lot of work done tried
something new a new style with the Vlog
like cozy calm like I took y'all with me
when I had to do my work on my laptop
and then I went to the gym afterwards a
little bit of leg day definitely gonna
fill up tomorrow we did sleds so we did
weighted ABS at the end and then we also
did
sleds so that's definitely going to be
uh something in the next two days it's
nothing but grinding right now um like I
said in the last Vlog I um I did have a
a drink or two you know what I'm saying
and um I'm not proud of it but you know
I it's not like somebody was holding
something to my head and making me do it
like I did it of course course but um
that ain't happening again at least not
for a good a good while I have no I have
no in goal when it comes to or intaking
like liquor and any type of alcohol like
that it's just like I've grown from it
like when I did it like when I've done
it even in the moment like I'm still
kind of just like what was the point cuz
when I come home I'm just like I wasted
time like I mean of course it's made
memories and stuff but it's not like
memories that have been like oh my my
God that's the most fun I've ever had in
my life know they've just been memories
like oh okay that was cool
so it's just time to go back into that
hole not the dark hole just back into
that hole of you know what I've been
doing this whole time I never stopped I
just had a drink or two you know what
I'm saying and ain't no point ain't no
need cuz I literally gained nothing from
it and when I go to the gym the next day
I just feel like a piece of [__] cuz I'm
just like what was that even for you
feel me so
but I just want to be completely open
with you guys like I promise like it
ain't none of that going on no more like
at least not for now like I'm not saying
I'll never do it again but I'm just
saying for the meantime for what I see
and what I want for myself to you feel
me go to that next
level that that just has to get cut out
there's no point I don't gain anything
from it I end up having pointless
conversation with people off of it like
don't get me wrong I've had great
conversations off of it but there's no
value behind it cuz after that is going
like little do you know you'll forget
that person sooner or later like the
conversations that I have had with
people in the past and even of recently
when I've had a drink I could tell you
their names I don't know anybody like
it's just like a a drink when you're
outside or something like that is
basically like a album filler to me not
every song hits they got to hit a
certain amount of tracks or a certain
amount of records for their album that's
basically what the drink is like some
nights it's going to be hits when you
have it and then some nights it's not
not but it's like I rather have none of
those nights and I rather just have
straight hits when it comes to what I
want for me and that's not liquor and
that's not anything of that nature
anything intoxicated I don't want
nothing to do with it when I say hits I
mean like making sure that I did the
best I could today make sure I went to
the gym make sure I ate what I was
supposed to eat make sure I took in
enough water make sure my family is okay
I mean I'm not excuse me I'm not in the
best position to take care of my entire
family and I know that's a lot of
people's goal that's one of my goals um
but I don't have the biggest family in
the world I do have a lot of siblings
the world cuz like that's just it's a
long story so long story short like all
I want to do one day is just be able to
take care of all my family and stuff
like that and that's I think that's
literally everybody's goal you know what
I'm saying so but me going outside and
you know what I'm saying getting a drink
or two like I'm not sitting here
degrading anybody that does it cuz I
mean that would make me a hypocrite and
I've been a hypocrite in the past I used
to say don't do this and I'll go do it
anyways I was just being a weirdo back
then like not really a weirdo but just
insecure with myself when I saw other
people doing stuff that I did I didn't
like it and I don't know it just weird I
had my own problems that I was dealing
with more of the story is just like if
you really want something you got to
really go get it and make it happen cuz
it's not going to fall in your lap like
I've said this so many times like to so
many people even and even in my videos
I've said it too yeah I'm here to tell
you right now the whole outside life I'm
not going to sit here and act like I've
never been outside outside I used to be
outside every day like I'm here to tell
you like I've experienced these things
and that's why I share them with you
guys cuz it's just why I sit here and
waste your time when I can sit here and
let you know ahead of time for the
younger people that watch me anything
that has to do with loud music liquor
and hoes bro cut it out like you gain
nothing from it I had a situation where
one time I ran into somebody outside
whatever I don't know who they were they
were just like oh he's handsome D thank
you ma'am keep it pushing I ran into him
again later this time around she's
trying to do something with me and I'm
like n like I'm cool folks that I'm with
is like you tripping if that was me I
would have did it okay gang that's to
you I'm a different type of person like
in the past of course I had to live and
I had to learn so you know what I'm
saying like I done did things in my past
I'm not perfect you know what I'm saying
so but now that I am who I am today like
I'm fully comfortable in my skin and I
don't want to crawl out of it anymore
and I love who I am inside of my own
skin now no I don't want to go do this
with this girl that I don't know like
I'm cool like you can have that like
I've graduated from that I've moved on
from that it's no need to do this like
it's pointless relations like if that's
what you want and I'm the man when it
come to throwing the alleyoop like huh
you can have her or huh you can have
this person you know what I'm saying
like I take no offense to it like if
somebody find me attractive and I don't
care for it Like H boom but I'm I'm just
going to completely cut all of that out
by just not being in the way of anything
or not being outside cuz like what am I
gaining from it why am I sitting
here having fun but I'm really sitting
here thinking like damn I could be like
doing something way better right now I
could literally be by myself being by
myself is my favorite thing and that's
really why like I just don't care to be
around people anymore honestly and it's
not that I'm against it I just simply do
not care I know one day it'll change but
I just feel like I don't I don't see it
happening anytime soon cuz I like who I
am now I really do cuz back then I
genuinely hated myself and I just would
do things to take my mind off of
anything that had to do with me I done
did it all you know what I'm saying to
an extent though to an extent I done did
a lot of stuff and I don't regret
anything I've definitely done harm in
the past you know what I'm saying and
I'm not proud of it but I'm not the type
of man that's going to sit here and act
like I'm picture perfect and I've never
done anything cuz that's fraud and I'm
type I'm Type [__] that's going to tell
you what it is every single time you
know what I'm saying like I don't really
care like I don't hold back like all my
family know like oh like if something if
something need to be said Nate going to
say it like all my family know that
that's just the hand I was dealt as I've
grown up so don't be scared to tell the
people that you love which what needs to
be said you know what I'm saying like
don't hold back just tell them and if
they take it the wrong way obviously
they need some fixing and you need some
fixing because you not being able to
realize that this person can't take the
truth that says something about you cuz
if you're with somebody and you rock
with them they should be able to take
the truth like as long as you speaking
the truth you ain't lying on them as
long as you ain't you know what I'm
saying doing no foul [__] to your people
bro and you keeping it a being with him
bro it's longevity with that it's really
longevity to have like just those couple
of friends those couple of family
members that you can really talk to
about certain things and stuff like that
but don't ever say too much to nobody
even if you're world feels like it's
ending bro I promise you it's not cuz
I've been there bro I've been there done
that like on the edge it's a lot of
stuff that goes on that no nobody know
about but I've been there before bro and
when I say I was on the edge I think you
can pick up on what I was saying I've
been there to where the light was almost
going Brody I'm here to tell you it's
not worth it you gain nothing from it
just stay focused if you're not focused
it's okay take it day by day that's like
my go-to phrase I say it in the gym all
the time I ain't thinking about what
exercise I'm GNA be doing on December
17th at 2:03 p.m. I'm thinking about
what I'm going to do tomorrow after I
finish my day today so just don't
compare your life to nobody don't
compare your don't compare anything that
you have going on to anybody that is the
root of all evil comparison comparison
is the thief of Joy so be careful with
what you're thinking be careful with
what you're saying the power of the
tongue is real the power of the tongue
is how I have you watching me right
now no [__] [__] like real talk so
y'all be safe y'all be careful and I'll
see y'all in the next video appreciate
everything